[
    { "question" : "打", "answer" : "hit", "pronunciation" : "dǎ", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "吃", "answer" : "eat", "pronunciation" : "chī", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "喝", "answer" : "drink", "pronunciation" : "hē", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "睡", "answer" : "sleep", "pronunciation" : "shuì", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "洗", "answer" : "wash", "pronunciation" : "xǐ", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "看", "answer" : "look", "pronunciation" : "kàn", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "听", "answer" : "listen", "pronunciation" : "tīng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "说", "answer" : "speak", "pronunciation" : "shuō", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "玩", "answer" : "play", "pronunciation" : "wán", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "学", "answer" : "learn", "pronunciation" : "xué", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "坐", "answer" : "sit", "pronunciation" : "zuò", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "跑", "answer" : "run", "pronunciation" : "pǎo", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "运", "answer" : "deliver", "pronunciation" : "yùn", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "手", "answer" : "give", "pronunciation" : "shǒu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "见", "answer" : "see", "pronunciation" : "jiàn", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "出", "answer" : "go out", "pronunciation" : "chū", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "进", "answer" : "go in", "pronunciation" : "jìn", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "放", "answer" : "put", "pronunciation" : "fàng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "把", "answer" : "hold", "pronunciation" : "bǎ", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "打电话", "answer" : "make a phone call", "pronunciation" : "dǎ diàn huà", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "打车", "answer" : "hail a taxi", "pronunciation" : "dǎ chē", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "买", "answer" : "buy", "pronunciation" : "mǎi", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "开", "answer" : "open", "pronunciation" : "kāi", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "关", "answer" : "close", "pronunciation" : "guān", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "下", "answer" : "go down", "pronunciation" : "xià", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "上", "answer" : "go up", "pronunciation" : "shàng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "找", "answer" : "look for", "pronunciation" : "zhǎo", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "住", "answer" : "live", "pronunciation" : "zhù", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "饭馆", "answer" : "eatery", "pronunciation" : "fàn guǎn", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "吃饭", "answer" : "have a meal", "pronunciation" : "chī fàn", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "请", "answer" : "invite", "pronunciation" : "qǐng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "想", "answer" : "want", "pronunciation" : "xiǎng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "预定", "answer" : "reserve", "pronunciation" : "yù dìng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "改", "answer" : "change", "pronunciation" : "gǎi", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "检查", "answer" : "check", "pronunciation" : "jiǎn chá", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "结束", "answer" : "end", "pronunciation" : "jié shù", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "开始", "answer" : "start", "pronunciation" : "kāi shǐ", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "等", "answer" : "wait", "pronunciation" : "děng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "进行", "answer" : "proceed", "pronunciation" : "jìn xíng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "帮助", "answer" : "help", "pronunciation" : "bāng zhù", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "送", "answer" : "send", "pronunciation" : "sòng", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "坐车", "answer" : "take a car", "pronunciation" : "zuò chē", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "忘记", "answer" : "forget", "pronunciation" : "wàng jì", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "接", "answer" : "pick up", "pronunciation" : "jiē", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "离开", "answer" : "leave", "pronunciation" : "lí kāi", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "回家", "answer" : "go home", "pronunciation" : "huí jiā", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "带", "answer" : "bring", "pronunciation" : "dài", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "介绍", "answer" : "introduce", "pronunciation" : "jiè shào", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "看见", "answer" : "see", "pronunciation" : "kàn jiàn", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "认识", "answer" : "know", "pronunciation" : "rèn shí", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "乘坐", "answer" : "ride", "pronunciation" : "chéng zuò", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "过来", "answer" : "come over", "pronunciation" : "guò lái", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "喜欢", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "xǐ huān", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "订购", "answer" : "order", "pronunciation" : "dìng gòu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "人", "answer" : "person", "pronunciation" : "rén", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "时间", "answer" : "time", "pronunciation" : "shí jiān", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "地方", "answer" : "place", "pronunciation" : "dì fāng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "事情", "answer" : "matter", "pronunciation" : "shì qing", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "东西", "answer" : "thing", "pronunciation" : "dōng xi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "钱", "answer" : "money", "pronunciation" : "qián", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "衣服", "answer" : "clothes", "pronunciation" : "yī fu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "食物", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "shí wù", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "饮料", "answer" : "beverage", "pronunciation" : "yǐn liào", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "水", "answer" : "water", "pronunciation" : "shuǐ", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "咖啡", "answer" : "coffee", "pronunciation" : "kā fēi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "茶", "answer" : "tea", "pronunciation" : "chá", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "牛奶", "answer" : "milk", "pronunciation" : "niú nǎi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "果汁", "answer" : "fruit juice", "pronunciation" : "guǒ zhī", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "餐具", "answer" : "tableware", "pronunciation" : "cān jù", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "手机", "answer" : "cellphone", "pronunciation" : "shǒu jī", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "电脑", "answer" : "computer", "pronunciation" : "diàn nǎo", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "相机", "answer" : "camera", "pronunciation" : "xiàng jī", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "电视", "answer" : "TV", "pronunciation" : "diàn shì", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "音乐", "answer" : "music", "pronunciation" : "yīn yuè", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "图书馆", "answer" : "library", "pronunciation" : "tú shū guǎn", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "学校", "answer" : "school", "pronunciation" : "xué xiào", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "办公室", "answer" : "office", "pronunciation" : "bàn gōng shì", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "家庭", "answer" : "family", "pronunciation" : "jiā tíng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "假期", "answer" : "vacation", "pronunciation" : "jià qī", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "旅行", "answer" : "travel", "pronunciation" : "lǚ xíng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "汽车", "answer" : "car", "pronunciation" : "qì chē", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "公共汽车", "answer" : "bus", "pronunciation" : "gōng gòng qì chē", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "火车", "answer" : "train", "pronunciation" : "huǒ chē", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "飞机", "answer" : "airplane", "pronunciation" : "fēi jī", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "自行车", "answer" : "bicycle", "pronunciation" : "zì xíng chē", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "鞋子", "answer" : "shoes", "pronunciation" : "xié zi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "包", "answer" : "bag", "pronunciation" : "bāo", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "书", "answer" : "book", "pronunciation" : "shū", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "报纸", "answer" : "newspaper", "pronunciation" : "bào zhǐ", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "电影", "answer" : "movie", "pronunciation" : "diàn yǐng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "票", "answer" : "ticket", "pronunciation" : "piào", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "信", "answer" : "letter", "pronunciation" : "xìn", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "纸", "answer" : "paper", "pronunciation" : "zhǐ", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "钥匙", "answer" : "key", "pronunciation" : "yào shi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "眼镜", "answer" : "glasses", "pronunciation" : "yǎn jìng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "椅子", "answer" : "chair", "pronunciation" : "yǐ zi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "桌子", "answer" : "table", "pronunciation" : "zhuō zi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "床", "answer" : "bed", "pronunciation" : "chuáng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "电梯", "answer" : "elevator", "pronunciation" : "diàn tī", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "楼梯", "answer" : "stairs", "pronunciation" : "lóu tī", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "窗户", "answer" : "window", "pronunciation" : "chuāng hù", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "门", "answer" : "door", "pronunciation" : "mén", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "空气", "answer" : "air", "pronunciation" : "kōng", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "美丽", "answer" : "beautiful", "pronunciation" : "měi lì", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "帅气", "answer" : "handsome", "pronunciation" : "shuài qì", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "可爱", "answer" : "cute", "pronunciation" : "kě ài", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "聪明", "answer" : "smart", "pronunciation" : "cōng míng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "懒惰", "answer" : "lazy", "pronunciation" : "lǎn duò", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "勤劳", "answer" : "hardworking", "pronunciation" : "qín láo", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "耐心", "answer" : "patient", "pronunciation" : "nài xīn", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "热情", "answer" : "passionate", "pronunciation" : "rè qíng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "冷静", "answer" : "calm", "pronunciation" : "lěng jìng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "幸福", "answer" : "happy", "pronunciation" : "xìng fú", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "不幸", "answer" : "unhappy", "pronunciation" : "bù xìng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "兴奋", "answer" : "excited", "pronunciation" : "xīng fèn", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "沮丧", "answer" : "pressed", "pronunciation" : "jǔ sàng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "紧张", "answer" : "nervous", "pronunciation" : "jǐn zhāng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "放松", "answer" : "relaxed", "pronunciation" : "fàng sōng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "活泼", "answer" : "lively", "pronunciation" : "huó pō", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "安静", "answer" : "quiet", "pronunciation" : "ān jìng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "平静", "answer" : "calm", "pronunciation" : "píng jìng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "温暖", "answer" : "warm", "pronunciation" : "wēn nuǎn", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "寒冷", "answer" : "cold", "pronunciation" : "hán lěng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "舒适", "answer" : "comfortable", "pronunciation" : "shū shì", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "不舒服", "answer" : "uncomfortable", "pronunciation" : "bù shū fú", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "干净", "answer" : "clean", "pronunciation" : "gān jìng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "脏", "answer" : "dirty", "pronunciation" : "zāng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "整洁", "answer" : "neat", "pronunciation" : "zhěng jié", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "杂乱", "answer" : "messy", "pronunciation" : "zá luàn", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "美味", "answer" : "licious", "pronunciation" : "měi wèi", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "难吃", "answer" : "bad-tasting", "pronunciation" : "nán chī", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "甜", "answer" : "sweet", "pronunciation" : "tián", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "苦", "answer" : "bitter", "pronunciation" : "kǔ", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "辣", "answer" : "spicy", "pronunciation" : "là", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "酸", "answer" : "sour", "pronunciation" : "suān", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "咸", "answer" : "salty", "pronunciation" : "xián", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "香", "answer" : "fragrant", "pronunciation" : "xiāng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "臭", "answer" : "stinky", "pronunciation" : "chòu", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "新", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "xīn", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "旧", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "jiù", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "老", "answer" : "aged", "pronunciation" : "lǎo", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "年轻", "answer" : "young", "pronunciation" : "nián qīng", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "成熟", "answer" : "mature", "pronunciation" : "chéng shú", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "非常", "answer" : "extremely", "pronunciation" : "fēi cháng", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "很", "answer" : "quite", "pronunciation" : "hěn", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "太", "answer" : "too", "pronunciation" : "tài", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "真", "answer" : "really", "pronunciation" : "zhēn", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "不", "answer" : "not", "pronunciation" : "bù", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "都", "answer" : "all", "pronunciation" : "dōu", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "还", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "hái", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "已经", "answer" : "already", "pronunciation" : "yǐ jīng", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "再", "answer" : "again", "pronunciation" : "zài", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "差不多", "answer" : "almost", "pronunciation" : "chà bù duō", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "竟然", "answer" : "unexpectedly", "pronunciation" : "jìng rán", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "可能", "answer" : "possibly", "pronunciation" : "kě néng", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "并且", "answer" : "furthermore", "pronunciation" : "bìng qiě", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "一起", "answer" : "together", "pronunciation" : "yì qǐ", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "分别", "answer" : "respectively", "pronunciation" : "fēn bié", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "然后", "answer" : "afterwards", "pronunciation" : "rán hòu", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "现在", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "xiàn zài", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "立刻", "answer" : "immediately", "pronunciation" : "lì kè", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "一直", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "yì zhí", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "刚刚", "answer" : "just now", "pronunciation" : "gāng gāng", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "终于", "answer" : "finally", "pronunciation" : "zhōng yú", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "其实", "answer" : "actually", "pronunciation" : "qí shí", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "不过", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "bù guò", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "只是", "answer" : "only", "pronunciation" : "zhǐ shì", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "不然", "answer" : "otherwise", "pronunciation" : "bù rán", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "先", "answer" : "first", "pronunciation" : "xiān", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "后来", "answer" : "later", "pronunciation" : "hòu lái", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "一定", "answer" : "definitely", "pronunciation" : "yí dìng", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "大概", "answer" : "probably", "pronunciation" : "dà gài", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "一下子", "answer" : "all at once", "pronunciation" : "yí xià zi", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "其他", "answer" : "other", "pronunciation" : "qí tā", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "恐怕", "answer" : "probably", "pronunciation" : "kǒng pà", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "以前", "answer" : "before", "pronunciation" : "yǐ qián", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "以后", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "yǐ hòu", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "同时", "answer" : "at the same time", "pronunciation" : "tóng shí", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "多么", "answer" : "how", "pronunciation" : "duō me", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "总是", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "zǒng shì", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "大概", "answer" : "probably", "pronunciation" : "dà gài", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "完全", "answer" : "completely", "pronunciation" : "wán quán", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "十分", "answer" : "extremely", "pronunciation" : "shí fēn", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "马上", "answer" : "immediately", "pronunciation" : "mǎ shàng", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "甚至", "answer" : "even", "pronunciation" : "shèn zhì", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "然而", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "rán ér", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "而且", "answer" : "moreover", "pronunciation" : "ér qiě", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "但是", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "dàn shì", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "因此", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "yīn cǐ", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "虽然", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "suī rán", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "如果", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "rú guǒ", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "然后", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "rán hòu", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "所以", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "suǒ yǐ", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "而已", "answer" : "that's all", "pronunciation" : "ér yǐ", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "不过", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "bù guò", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "一般来说", "answer" : "generally speaking", "pronunciation" : "yì bān lái shuō", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "即使", "answer" : "even if", "pronunciation" : "jí shǐ", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "因为", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "yīn wèi", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "所以说", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "suǒ yǐ shuō", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "其实", "answer" : "actually", "pronunciation" : "qí shí", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "并且", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "bìng qiě", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "可是", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "kě shì", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "要是", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "yào shì", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "不仅", "answer" : "not only", "pronunciation" : "bù jǐn", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "至少", "answer" : "at least", "pronunciation" : "zhì shǎo", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "另外", "answer" : "furthermore", "pronunciation" : "lìng wài", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "毕竟", "answer" : "after all", "pronunciation" : "bì jìng", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "换句话说", "answer" : "in other words", "pronunciation" : "huàn jù huà shuō", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "无论如何", "answer" : "anyway", "pronunciation" : "wú lùn rú hé", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "假如", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "jiǎ rú", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "如此", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "rú cǐ", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "别的", "answer" : "other", "pronunciation" : "bié de", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "哪怕", "answer" : "even if", "pronunciation" : "nǎ pà", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "另一方面", "answer" : "on the other hand", "pronunciation" : "lìng yī fāng miàn", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "不管", "answer" : "no matter", "pronunciation" : "bù guǎn", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "反而", "answer" : "instead", "pronunciation" : "fǎn ér", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "才", "answer" : "only", "pronunciation" : "cái", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "接着", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "jiē zhe", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "于是", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "yú shì", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "随着", "answer" : "along with", "pronunciation" : "suí zhe", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "同时", "answer" : "at the same time", "pronunciation" : "tóng shí", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "大概", "answer" : "probably", "pronunciation" : "dà gài", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "因而", "answer" : "thus", "pronunciation" : "yīn ér", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "反正", "answer" : "anyway", "pronunciation" : "fǎn zhèng", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "或许", "answer" : "perhaps", "pronunciation" : "huò xǔ", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "不然", "answer" : "otherwise", "pronunciation" : "bù rán", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "只要", "answer" : "as long as", "pronunciation" : "zhǐ yào", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "既然", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "jì rán", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "无论", "answer" : "regardless of", "pronunciation" : "wú lùn", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "即便", "answer" : "even if", "pronunciation" : "jí biàn", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "如何", "answer" : "how", "pronunciation" : "rú hé", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "倘若", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "táng ruò", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "不停", "answer" : "non-stop", "pronunciation" : "bù tíng", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "多么", "answer" : "how", "pronunciation" : "duō me", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "偶然", "answer" : "accidentally", "pronunciation" : "ǒu rán", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "不光", "answer" : "not only", "pronunciation" : "bù guāng", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "若是", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "ruò shì", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "不怕", "answer" : "not afraid of", "pronunciation" : "bù pà", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "然", "answer" : "yet", "pronunciation" : "rán", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "怎么样", "answer" : "how about", "pronunciation" : "zěn me yàng", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "别说", "answer" : "not to mention", "pronunciation" : "bié shuō", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "纵然", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "zòng rán", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "总之", "answer" : "in short", "pronunciation" : "zǒng zhī", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "反之", "answer" : "on the contrary", "pronunciation" : "fǎn zhī", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "多少", "answer" : "how many", "pronunciation" : "duō shǎo", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "除非", "answer" : "unless", "pronunciation" : "chú fēi", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "譬如", "answer" : "for example", "pronunciation" : "pì rú", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]